Hubby, save me!
Lin Zai!
Brother!
- Help!
- Lin Zai!
It's not possible! This way!
Quick! Go!
Hurry up, Lin Zai!
This way!
Over here!
Up! Up!
Brother, it won't open!
Brother! The door's open, quick!
You bastard.
It's not safe for us to be here.
We must hurry and find a new exit.
I just saw the floor plan in the hallway.
I know where the exit is.
Brother.
Don't worry, I will definitely get you out.
If you say it'll happen,
then it'll definitely happen!
Come on!
Lin Zai!
Brother!
Go! You must live on!
Go!
Let me be!
Brother...
Live on...
My name is Lin Zai.
22 days ago,
the zombie crisis broke out.
It destroyed my life,
and took away my parents.
Just now,
it took away my last family.
Now, I've been bitten, too.
It's all over.
They say,
after being bitten,
you can stay awake for a few hours at most.
It hurts this much.
And it's so cold.
You'll slowly forget who you are.
I'm probably...
on my way to the end.
Hubby, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Your lips are all pale.
Why are you sweating so much?
I'm good.
Please! Don't kill me!
Don't kill me! Please!
- Please don't kill him!
- Please!
Hubby!
- No immunogen found.
- Hubby!
Continue with the search.
I didn't turn into a zombie.
You must live on.
[Fortune]
Brother...
I will definitely live on well.
Even if it's just for one day.
[Apocalypse Log 1]
[Six Months Later]
Lin Zai, come here for a second.
Okay. Coming.
What's up, Li?
I changed the bulb, why isn't it working?
- Let me take a look.
- You gotta fix it quick.
Zombies got in last night.
- Huh?
- Don't worry.
Chen handled them all.
Chen is the best.
Here, give it to me.
Careful now.
Go on, try it.
Awesome.
- Come on, let's grab food.
- Okay.
A college kid really can make things work.
I only know how to
change light bulbs or fix faucets.
For this kind of sophisticated work,
we still have to rely on you.
- Li.
- Yeah?
You're the one with super strength.
Carrying me up
to the fifth floor without panting.
At crucial moments,
you are much more useful than me.
You little bastard.
Are you implying that
I'm all brawn and no brains?
- No, no.
- Next time when we carry supplies,
you're carrying twice the load.
Otherwise, don't bother coming back.
And no food for you.
I was just about to go in and call you.
- Time to eat!
- Grandma Qiu, let me help.
People need to eat.
Only when you are fed will you be able to work.
Today, we have the sparrow meat
you've been craving.
Don't rush, we'll eat together
when Chen's back.
Where is Chen?
Chen...
Chen should be in the backyard.
Then I'll go get her.
Okay.
Chen, food's ready!
Good thing you suggested
adding a few more defenses yesterday.
Otherwise, we would've been
attacked last night.
I'm glad it's useful.
But we still can't let our guard down.
All done.
Don't worry.
Our camp's location is hidden.
Just a zombie or two passing by occasionally.
I'm very equipped to deal with them.
You're the best.
I still have to check the other traps.
You go eat first.
All right, be careful.
Brother...
You must be protecting me in heaven,
keeping me from turning into a zombie.
Before that day comes,
I promise I will live on well.
Go!
Let me be!
Go! Let me be!
Don't touch him!
What are you doing?
What if he's a zombie?
Looks like he's not infected.
Just some physical injuries and scrapes.
Seems like he fell from somewhere.
Probably has some internal injuries
and fractures, too.
To be able to make it to our camp,
He probably encountered
quite a few zombies along the way.
Can he be saved?
Hard to say.
But it's best we don't get involved in this.
Camp supplies are already low.
Look at his gear.
It's hard to say
if he's an apocalyptic raider or not.
We have to prioritize the safety of our camp.
Bro, I'm sorry.
As much as we want to,
we really can't help.
Sorry about this.
Wow.
Bandages.
Such a big bundle of climbing rope.
And a small flashlight.
He's definitely not an ordinary person.
Food.
Tools.
All things our camp needs.
Other than raiders,
probably no one would
carry such complete equipment
while wandering outside.
He really has everything.
But at a time like this,
it's still better to be careful.
After all, it took us a lot
to finally build up this camp.
Ugh. That's true.
No matter what time it is,
humans always find enemies in their own kind.
Humans always find enemies in their own kind.
All right. Stop overthinking it.
Even in peaceful times,
if someone collapses on the roadside,
not everyone would be a Samaritan.
Let alone now.
Captain Chen's judgment isn't wrong.
Your desire to save people isn't wrong either.
I know. I just...
Forget it. Let's not talk about him.
What else is in there? Let me see.
Hey.
This kid's toy.
It's a bit too childish.
Just right for a young college boy like you.
It's yours.
College boys find it childish, too.
Well...
Oh, how about this?
This is a trendy watch.
Thanks, Li.
When the game console is fixed,
I'll let you play it first.
That's more like it.
You'd better not be a raider.
Otherwise, my good intentions
will have caused a disaster.
Hey! How are you doing?
Hang in there!
Hey! Wake up!
Wake up! Hey!
Hey! Don't die in front me!
I went through a lot to take you back here!
I don't want my efforts to go in vain!
Hey! Wake up!